♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪
=The One=
=Episode 21=
(Five years later)
Here's the divorce agreement.
My client has just one condition.
She wants custody of the child.
Fine.
But I have one condition.
She leaves with nothing.
And pays me 20 million yuan.
You... you're shameless.
You're the one who cheated!
You...
Wangfu Garden, Apt. 1901.
Every month,
you give influencer Ms. Li 200,000 yuan.
A college student at No. 9 Wutong Court.
80,000 yuan a month.
Last month at a nightclub,
you assaulted a server.
I have the video.
You'd be looking at three to five years.
I'll submit the HD copy
as evidence in court.
Who are you?
What, playing the hero?
Mr. Wang.
You owe 20 million in gambling debts
back in Aocheng.
Planning to use her money to pay it off?
You're...
Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Cheng!
Give me one more month.
I'll pay you back. I promise.
If you hadn't hit her just now,
we might've had room to negotiate.
You're with Mr. Cheng?
I'll sign! I'll sign! I'll sign!
I'll sign! I'll sign!
Just give me one month!
Are you still living at...
I'll have my driver take you.
Someone's picking me up.
No need, Mr. Cheng.
Mom!
We've been waiting forever!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mr. Cheng.
(Mom, Daddy picked me up today)
(and bought me lots of yummy snacks.)
Thanks for picking Tangtang up.
But you shouldn't have Tangtang
calling you Dad.
Is Tangtang's father...
Cheng Lin?
I told you.
I adopted Tangtang.
I'll take her back
to the children's home.
Thank you for all you've done, Ms. Su.
I only did
what any lawyer should do.
She may not have come into this world
the way her parents
had hoped,
but I want her to know
her mother was very brave.
I hope she grows up
happy and carefree.
Don't worry. We'll take care of her.
Whenever you have time, Ms. Su,
come visit her.
I will.
Whenever we can,
we'll come visit the children.
Sir.
Can I adopt her?
(Su Yan.)
(Tell me.)
(What would make you feel better?)
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪
♪Memories pile up, moment by moment♪
♪One careless word brings my walls down♪
♪I escape the past, then fall back in♪
♪Longing twists into a hopeless knot♪
♪Pulled by the past
till my world fades out♪
♪I hum this song alone♪
♪Counting every fleeting moment♪
♪Every corner still reminds me of you♪
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪